A Guide to the Papers of the Alpha Kappa Psi Fraternity, Alpha Gamma Chapter at the University of Virginia ca. 1923-1952
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Alpha Kappa Psi Fraternity, Alpha Gamma Chapter at the University of Virginia ca. 1923-1952
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-23/4/13.442
This collection consists of the records of the Alpha Gamma Chapter of the Alpha Kappa Psi Fraternity at the University of Virginia, ca. 1923-1952, ca. 400 items (2 Hollinger boxes, ca. 1 linear foot).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Scope and Content
These papers include correspondence, financial records, membership records, newsletters of various chapters, autobiographies of members, bulletins from fraternity headquarters, constitution and by-laws, news clippings, programs, and photographs.
Contents List
- Account Sheets ca. 1929-1937 (Box-folder 1:1)
- Account Book, etc. 1929-1939 (Box-folder 1:2)
- Autobiographies of Members of Alpha Kappa Psi at the University of Virginia ca. 1940s (Box-folder 1:3)
- Blank Forms n.d. (Box-folder 1:4)
- Bulletins 1936-1943, 1950 (Box-folder 1:5)
- Certificate of Demit Records 1930-1936, 2 volumes (Box-folder 1:6)
- Christmas Cards 1941-1942, n.d. (Box-folder 1:7)
- Constitution and By-laws 1935, 1939, n.d. (Box-folder 1:8)
- Correspondence 1936-1941 (Box-folder 1:9)
- Correspondence 1942 (Box-folder 1:10)
- Correspondence 1943, 1945 (Folder 2:1)
- Correspondence 1949-1952 (Box-folder 2:2)
- Directory of Alpha Kappa Psi - Membership in D.C. Area 1951 Sep. (Box-folder 2:3)
- Membership Records 1923-1926 (Box-folder 2:4)
- Membership Records 1926-1929 (Box-folder 2:5)
- Membership Records 1929-1933 (Box-folder 2:6)
- Membership Records 1933-1937, 1951 (Box-folder 2:7)
- Miscellaneous 1942, 1952, n.d. (Box-folder 2:8)
- News clippings 1936-1940, 1952 (Box-folder 2:9)
- Newsletters - Alpha Gamma News at the University of Virginia 1942 (Box-folder 2:10)
- Newsletters from Other Chapters, arranged by name of chapter 1937-1943, 1951 (Box-folder 2:11)
- Photographs 1938, 1947-1948, n.d. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Pledge Forms Signed 1940-1943 (Box-folder 2:13)
- Pledge Ritual and Examination Programs (Box-folder 2:14)
- Programs 1941-1950 (Box-folder 2:15)
- Questionnaire on Schools of Commerce n.d. (Box-folder 2:16)
- Resolution of Sympathy upon the Death of Member, Alfredo Navarro 1936 (Box-folder 2:17)
- Ribbon and Sign for Alpha Kappa Psi n.d. (Box-folder 2:18)
- Speech by J. Irving Cason - "Establishing and Maintaining an Accounting Organization" 1943 May 24 (Box-folder 2:19)
- Stock Market Contest 1941, n.d. (Box-folder 2:20)